让你再万岁
Heil this.
哥  你杀了希特勒
Dude, you killed Hitler.
太棒了
Awesome.
(忆往昔)
救人猎魔
Saving people and hunting things,
这是我们的生活
this is our life.
我觉得我们让世界更美好了
I think we make the world a better place.
我这辈子都在逃避猎魔
I spent my life running from hunting.
你原来很厉害  是吧
You were good at this, weren't you?
非常厉害
Very.
问题是  猎人
The thing is, Hunters?
不管多厉害  最终结果都是一样的
No matter how good they are, they all end up the same way.
不
No!
鲍比
Bobby!
我很了解你  迪恩·温彻斯特
I know all about you, Dean Winchester.
别伤害她  她是被恶魔附身了
Don't hurt her. That's a human possessed by a demon.
[咒语]
驱逐我
An exorcism?
等着下地狱吧
You're gonna burn in hell.
[咒语]
-那馅饼呢  -待会儿的吧
- How about some pie? - Maybe later.
自从妈妈离开  你一直有点...暴躁
Ever since Mom left, you've been a little, uh, cranky.
她拿了点现金
What, she took some cash,
她拿走了手机  却不接
she took a cellphone she doesn't answer,
然后抛下我们跑路了
and she bailed on us.
有时候分开一阵  对一个家庭更好
You know, sometimes families do better after a little time apart.
哪个家庭  曼森家族吗
Yeah? Yeah, who? The Mansons?
(如今)
(马尼托巴  埃莫森  1980年)
这
So...
就是你家吗
this is your house?
你指路指得很棒
Look, you did a great job of pointing directions,
但说说话会更好
but words are helpful.
还有名字呢  我叫玛丽·温彻斯特
And names. Like me? I'm Mary. Winchester.
阿沙·福克斯
Asa. Fox.
好名字
That's a great name.
你不会有事的
You're gonna be fine.
我知道感觉不像  但是真的
I know it doesn't seem like it, but you are.
那东西是什么
What was that...thing?
狼人  我追踪他很久了
A werewolf. One I've been tracking for a long time.
我们有些过往  走吧
We had history. Come on.
狼人
Werewolf?
你杀狼人
You kill werewolves?
我猎杀过很多坏东西
I hunted a lot of bad things.
猎杀...过吗
"Hunted." like past tense?
我要退休了  其实按说我已经退休了
I'm retiring. Well, officially, I'm already retired.
就是想了结一些旧事
Just tying up a few loose ends.
但如果你退休了  那谁来救我这样的人
But if you retire, who's gonna save people like me?
你妈妈在吗
Uh, your mom in there?
很好
Good.
我给你...
Hey, let me just...
这样好多了
That's better.
够好了
Good enough.
去吧
Well, go on.
(特隆驱魔杀手仍在逃)
(致玛丽·温彻斯特)
(本地女人死于奇怪事故)
(登山客失踪)
(怪异事故导致死亡)
(鬼宅三人死亡)
(盐)
(本地凶杀案正在调查中  警方向公众寻求帮助)
(格拉斯通男子被杀)
(残忍谋杀案震惊警方  被害人遗骸在公园被发现)
(失踪)
(失踪孩子找到)
你知道有新车出产的吧
Hey, you know they make new cars, right?
我不要新车  这是我的幸运座驾
I don't want a new car. This is my lucky car.
(潜水员在马尼托巴湖中搜索失踪家庭)
(警方怀疑动物袭击)
(可怕动物袭击  小男孩遗骸被发现  当局正在调查  并向公众发布了警告)
[邪恶力量 第12季第6集]
网飞
Ahh, Netflix,
今天我休假  你要向我推荐什么呢
what do you recommend to fill my day off?
说吧
Speak to me.
你们看上去好惨  怎么了
You look terrible. What's wrong?
当然  我们很想进来
Sure, we'd love to come in.
你好
Hey there.
我们刚在布鲁金斯完成猎魔
Yeah, we just, uh, finished a hunt in Brookings.
就不能先洗个澡再来吗
And you couldn't take a shower first?
想回家前先来看看你
Figured we'd stop by on the way home,
见见你  克莱尔  艾莉克斯
see you, Claire, and Alex.
那敢情好啊
Aw, that's fun.
很遗憾  她俩去奥马哈度周末了
Unfortunately, the girls are in Omaha for the weekend,
去听什么电台司令的演唱会
being angsty at a Radiohead concert.
但我可以给你们吃的
But I can feed you.
好啊
Yes. All right.
我们上次见面之后
Since the last time we saw you?
我杀了希特勒
I killed Hitler.
谢谢了
Thank you?
不客气
You're welcome.
乔迪  你这是在看小妞电影吗
Jody, you watching some kind of chick flick here?
迪恩  我是个妞嘛
Well, Dean, I'm a chick.
不不  你是警长女汉子
No. No, no, you're -- you're a badass sheriff chick.
你不是浪漫喜剧妞  等等  你是吗
You're not a-a rom com chick. Wait, are you a rom com chick?
你是吗
Are you?
他更偏向于
He's more of a, uh...
日本动画AV妞
animated Japanese erotica chick.
真假
Really?
我得先告别如此精彩的对话
I need to leave this scintillating conversation.
别跟她说那个啊
Don't tell her that.
说什么
Don't tell her what?
她可是乔迪
It's Jody, man.
哥们  为你的癖好骄傲吧
Dude, be proud of your hobbies.
一定要骄傲
Make sure you are.
到球门区了  投啊
...in the end zone, throws it.
-乔迪  -触地得分  比赛结束
- Jody? - Touchdown! Game over!
乔迪  怎么了
Jody, what's up?
我一个朋友死了
Friend of mine died.
谁
Who?
阿沙·福克斯
Asa Fox.
阿沙·福克斯  这名字怎么耳熟呢
Asa Fox. Why does that name sound familiar?
埃伦以前在旅馆不是经常
Isn't he the guy that Ellen used to tell stories about
讲他的事吗
back at the Roadhouse?
是啊  据说他一晚上杀了五个温迪戈
Yeah. Supposedly, he killed, like, five Wendigos in a night.
是啊
Yeah.
他是个猎人
Yeah, he was a Hunter.
他几个月前来到了镇上
He, uh, he rolled into town a few months back,
还想骗我他是联调局探员福克斯·莫德
tried to convince me he was FBI Agent Fox Mulder.
他当时在追一群食尸鬼  我帮了忙
He was chasing a pack of ghouls, and I helped.
之后他就经常过来
He'd pass through every once in a while after that,
我们会一起喝杯咖啡什么的
and we'd grab co-- coffee or...something.
他是个好人
Oh, he was a good man.
今晚守夜
The -- the wake's tonight, and, um,
明天他们撒盐焚尸
they're gonna salt and burn the body tomorrow.
真不敢相信我刚把那当作常事说了出来
I can't believe I just said that like it's something normal.
我们跟你一起去
Well, we're gonna come with you.
嗯
Yeah.
不用了  我没事的
You don't have -- I'll be fine.
乔迪  我们知道你会没事
Yeah, no, Jody, we -- we know you'll be fine, but...
我们从不参加猎人集会  除了是泡酒吧
You know, we never go to Hunter gatherings, outside of bars.
老爸总说他们只会惹麻烦
Dad always said they were trouble, so...
是啊  让我们跟去算是帮我们忙了
Yes, you'd be doing us a favor if you let us tag along.
谢谢
Thank you.
你俩得去收拾收拾
You're gonna have to get cleaned up
否则我才不要跟你们一起坐五小时的车
before we spend five hours in the car together. Yeah.
五小时  我们去哪
Five hours? Where, uh, where we going?
(欢迎来到马尼托巴  埃莫森)
哦加拿大
O Canada.
好大的房子
That is a big house.
家族的房子  阿沙就是个普通人
Family home. Asa was just a guy.
伙计
Hey, buddy.
乔迪
Jody!
乔迪  谢谢你来
Oh, Jody, thanks for comin'.
洛琳  当然的  你还好吗
Loraine, of course. How you holding up?
这一屋吵闹的醉汉猎人
Well, it's a house full of loud, drunk Hunters...
而我儿子的死尸在客厅里
and my son's dead body is in the parlor.
但我还没割腕呢
But I haven't slit my wrists yet.
小小的胜利
Small victories.
我们很遗憾  节哀顺变
We're very sorry for your loss.
我知道
I know.
大家都这么说
Everyone's sorry.
这...肯定好玩
So...this is gonna be fun.
没标签  绝不是好事
No label. Well, that's a red flag.
非常安全  我自己酿的
Nah, fully safe. I home brewed it myself.
来  不是扭的
Here. Not a twist-off.
希望你喜欢比较猛的啤酒  伙计
Oh, hope you like strong beer, buddy.
不错
That's good.
迪恩·温彻斯特
Uh, Dean Winchester.
你是迪恩·温彻斯特
The Dean Winchester?
不可能
No freakin' way.
你不是死了吗  死四次了
Aren't you dead? Like, four times?
是啊  没死透
Yeah. It, uh, didn't take.
等等  你弟弟来了吗  萨姆
Wait. Your brother here? Sam?
嗯  他也还活着
Yeah, he's still alive, too. He's --
好吧  聊天愉快
Okay, good talk.
别介意埃维斯  他就那样
Yeah, sorry about Elvis. He's, uh...Elvis.
我是巴奇·希姆斯
I'm Bucky Sims.
兰迪  兰迪·布尔
Yeah. Randy. Randy Bull.
小心犄角
Watch out for the horns, right?
你俩是猎人
Uh, you two Hunters?
是的
Yes, sir.
-你认识阿沙吗  -不  没见过
- Did you know Asa? - No, no, I never met him,
但听过一些挺不可思议的传闻
but, uh, heard some crazy stories.
比如呢
Yeah? Like what?
拜托
Well, I mean, come on.
没人能一晚杀掉五个温迪戈
Nobody can take out five Wendigos in a night.
我们著名的朋友说那个字眼了
Our famous friend said the magic word.
喝酒喽
Drink, everybody.
"温迪戈"  那是...
"Wendigo"? Is that, uh --
又说了
Do it again.
好吧
Okay.
别再说了  否则我们撑不到白天了
Stop saying that or we're not gonna make it to morning.
不知道规矩
Didn't know the rules.
你如果觉得阿沙的故事不可思议
You think the stories about Asa are crazy,
真该听听关于你的传闻
you should hear what they say about you.
等等  你们是女巫养大的  却成了猎人
Wait, so you guys were raised by a witch, but you're Hunters?
对
Yep.
她是个好女巫
She was, like, a good witch.
很恩雅  那是90年代
Very Enya. It was the '90s.
好多水晶
Lots of crystals.
她教我猎女巫  坏女巫
She taught me to hunt witches. Uh, bad witches.
好吧  她教了你什么
Sure. And what did she teach you?
主要是怎么勾引男人
Uh, mostly how to seduce men.
她还教了他些魔法  那个更有用
She also taught him some magic, which is actually more useful.
还是勾引男人教得更多
Eh, mostly the men thing.
麦克斯
Max.
你是萨姆·温彻斯特吗  是吧
Are you Sam Winchester? You are, right?
太疯狂了
Oh, this is nuts.
埃维斯·凯茨
Uh, Elvis, um, Katz.
是这样
Look, so thing is,
我在美国有个朋友
I got this friend down in the States, right,
认识个女孩  那女孩认识你朋友盖思
who knows this girl who knew your pal Garth.
-盖思  -对
- Garth. - Yeah.
他说她说盖思说
And, well, he said that she said that Garth said
你曾被魔鬼附身
that you were possessed by the Devil?
就是路西法那个魔鬼
Like, Lucifer, the actual big, bad Devil,
你还活了下来
and you lived?
哥们  这么操蛋的事怎么能直接问人家
Dude, you don't just ask someone about something that messed up.
真的  别烦人家了
Seriously, back off.
但这多了不起啊
But it's pretty amazing, huh?
其实  并不是什么好经历
N-- It -- it's really not that amazing.
就是那么回事
It -- it just kind of is what it is.
我去拿瓶啤酒
I'm gonna get a-a beer.
你们不用吗  好
Yeah, you good? Yeah? Good.
你们怎么回事
So what's your guys' deal?
你能不能
Could...could you, like,
离我们远点
go away from us now?
这是货真价实的天使之刃
This is a real Angel Blade.
这人厉害啊
I mean, this guy was legit.
你知道大家都讲关于我们的传闻吗
Did you know people tell stories about us?
是啊  看来我们还算是传奇人物
Yeah. Apparently, we're a little bit legendary.
是啊  但阿沙也是
Yeah, but, I mean, so was Asa.
但猎魔出了岔子
Then a hunt went bad,
他就一个人吊死在了林子里一棵树上
and he ended up hanging from a tree, alone in the woods.
因公殉职  没有更好的死法了
He died on the job. No better way to go.
你真那么想吗
You really believe that?
是啊  怎么  你不吗
Yeah. What, you don't?
拜托  萨姆  我们又不是
I mean, come on, Sam, it's not like we're in
做"活到九十  美梦长眠"那行的
the "live till you're 90, die in your sleep" business.
这一行
This?
(悲剧惨死  8岁男孩遗骸找到  警方怀疑动物袭击)
(可怕动物袭击  小男孩遗骸被发现  当局正在调查  并向公众发布了警告)
(潜水员在马尼托巴湖中搜索失踪家庭)
只有一个结局
This only ends one way.
我们该回去了
We should get back.
嗯  别跟人说"温迪戈"
Yeah. Oh, uh, don't say "Wendigo" to anyone.
谢谢
Thank you.
还挺好的  是吧
That was nice, wasn't it?
阿沙逼我们滑旱冰
And Asa made us go roller skating,
那些食尸鬼差点杀了我们
and right after these ghouls almost got us.
我们三个  都鼻青脸肿的
So there's the three of us, all banged up,
却跟一群小青年在霓虹灯下滑旱冰
with a ton of ironic teenagers skating under these neon lights.
记得吗  乔迪
You remember this, Jody?
太有趣了
Oh, it was classic.
直到
I mean, you know,
你俩溜开  单独温柔乡去了
until you two snuck off for some sweet, sweet time alone.
是啊
Oh, yeah!
"单独温柔乡"
"Sweet, sweet time alone"?
你  乔迪  你没说
You, Jody? You didn't tell us
-你在跟阿沙恋爱  -记得吧
- you were in a relationship with Asa. - Remember that.
就是大家玩玩  抱歉  洛琳
Oh, it was just -- it was just a casual thing. Sorry, Loraine.
阿沙一向受女士欢迎
Asa was always popular with the ladies.
-是啊  -我们妈妈可喜欢他了
- Yes, he was. - Our mom loved him.
她以前老念叨他的事
She used to talk about him all the time.
是吧
See?
而且你俩不在时我还要生活呢
And, you know, I do have a life when you guys aren't around.
还有谁要啤酒吗
Beer, anyone?
-不了  -我要
- I'm good. - Yeah.
-好  -而且  告诉你们  约会很难的
- Okay. - And, uh, here's a news flash -- dating is hard.
又不是说你俩一走我就变成了
It's not like I just turn into a boring small-town sheriff
无聊的小镇警长
when you guys are gone.
我也会做些事的
I do stuff.
知道啦  乔迪
Get it, Jody.
我猎魔  结识人  有时候...
I hunt. I meet people. Sometimes I...
不是什么大事  好吧
It was no big deal. Right?
你们不该意外
You shouldn't be surprised
我喜欢跟粗犷性感的男人在一起
that I'd enjoy the company of a ruggedly hot man.
-可不是  -这我没话说
- Amen to that. - Can't argue with that.
是啊
Yeah.
你显然应该拥有
Hey, you clearly deserve...
"单独的温柔乡"
...your sweet, sweet time alone.
也不总那么温柔
Well, I mean, it wasn't always sweet.
就是我们不会那么想你
Yeah. It's just not how we think of you. You know?
太好了  否则就太奇怪了
Good, 'cause that would honestly be weird.
没人说你不能约会
Nobody -- nobody said you can't date, right?
好吧
That's fair.
请进  别在门口待着
Come on in. Don't hover.
抱歉  我敲门了
Sorry, I knocked.
门开着
Door was open.
-你们怎么来了  -你怎么来了
- What are you doing here? - What are you doing here?
我们...阿沙是朋友的朋友
We, uh... Asa was a-a friend of a friend.
乔迪的朋友  乔迪  这是玛丽
Uh, friend of Jody's. Jody, Mary.
-妈妈  这是乔迪·米尔斯  -妈妈
- Mom, this is Jody Mills. - Mom?
-没错  -等等  你俩的妈妈吗
- Mom. - Wait, m-- Your mom?
嗯
Yeah.
我以为你...
I thought -- I thought you were...
是啊
I was.
很高兴认识你
It is so nice to meet you!
我要...
I'm gonna...I'm j--
我让你们一家人一起待会儿吧
I'm gonna give you guys some, um, some family time.
你都去哪了
Where you been?
到处走  我回劳伦斯了几天
All over. I went back to Lawrence for a few days.
然后
And then,
我在借助约翰的日记进行回溯
I've been using John's journal to retrace a few things.
想补上我错过的一切
Try to catch up on what I've missed.
你可以直接问我们啊
You could've just asked us, you know.
-迪恩  得了  -就是可以嘛
- Dean, come on. - She could've.
没事  他说得对  但是
It's okay. He's right. But...
这件事我得自己做
This is something I needed to do alone.
我
I...
听着  大部分我认识的人都死了
Listen...most of the people I knew are dead.
然后我记起了阿沙
And then I remembered Asa.
我遇见他时他还很小
He was so young when I met him,
我以为他肯定还活着
I thought he must still be around.
然后
And then...
我看到了他的死讯
I saw an article about his death,
所以
and, uh...
所以你一周偶尔给我们发个短信
So you'll text us once a week, maybe,
但为了见个死人不惜开车来加拿大
but you'll drive all the way to Canada to see some dead guy?
真是太棒了
Well, that's awesome.
我去透口气
I'm gonna get some air.
迪恩  等等
Dean, wait.
你没事吧
You okay?
好得很
Swell.
所以你来的这一路上一直跟我
Is that why you spent the entire ride up here telling me
详细得不能再详细地讲
in extreme, excruciating detail
你杀希特勒的过程
how you killed Hitler, but, uh,
却没说你妈妈起死回生了吗
you neglected to mention the fact that your mom is back from the dead?
是啊  这没什么的
Yeah, no big deal.
-撒谎  -乔迪
- That's a lie. - Jody...
或许这轮不到我说话  这事太了不起了
Look, maybe this isn't my place, and this is epic stuff,
但是
but, you know...
如果我儿子和丈夫能回来
if I could have my son and my husband back? I mean....
真正的回来
really back,
我真的愿意为此付出一切
I would give anything, absolutely anything, to have that.
但也会让我非常害怕
And it would scare the hell out of me.
是吗
Yeah?
是啊  因为如果我已经变了呢
Yeah. 'Cause what if I've changed?
如果他们变了呢
What if they changed?
如果一切不能如我所愿呢
What if it just didn't work out the way I wanted?
如果你想谈谈
If you wanna talk about anything,
什么事都行  我会陪你
absolutely anything, I'm here.
谢谢  乔迪
Thanks, Jody.
阿沙最喜欢了
Asa's favorite.
难喝死了
Tastes awful.
我是洛琳·福克斯  阿沙的妈妈
I'm Loraine Fox, Asa's mom.
玛丽·温彻斯特
Mary Winchester.
不  不可能
No, you're not.
阿沙跟我说过你
Asa told me about you, but...
但你该跟我一般大
you'd be my age.
怎么会
So how...
说来话长
It's a long story.
当然了
I'll bet.
-抱歉  -你是该抱歉
- I'm sorry - You should be.
我说了  阿沙跟我说过你
Like I said, Asa told me about you.
就是因为你  我儿子没成为宇航员
You're the reason my son didn't become an astronaut.
宇航员
Astronaut?
看
Here.
这是这些年来阿沙给你写的
Asa wrote those to you over the years
但没法寄出去  因为你太"神秘"了
but couldn't send them because you're so "mysterious"
(致玛丽·温彻斯特)
我救了他一命
I saved his life.
你要我怎么回答
What am I supposed to say to that?
你走后  阿沙变得那么...
After you, Asa got so...
猎魔成了他的全部
Hunting was his whole life.
他没结婚  没成家  要孩子
He never married, never had a family, kids.
现在
And now...
守夜愉快
Enjoy the wake.
你没事吧
Everything all right?
我没事
I'm fine.
没事的
It's fine.
真的吗
Are you sure?
阿沙小时候我救了他
I saved Asa when he was a boy.
这一切  都是因我而起
All of this, it's on me.
不  妈妈  他是自己做出了选择
Well, no. Obviously, Mom, he made his own decisions.
他帮了很多人
And he helped a lot of people, you know?
是啊  我也说不清
Yeah, I don't know.
我现在什么都不确定了
I just don't know anymore.
不论我走到哪  做什么
Everywhere I go and everything I do just...
都感觉不对
feels wrong.
但我会适应的
But I'll get used to it.
适应回到这里  我会的
Being back here, I will. I just --
妈妈  你不用解释什么  我懂的
Yeah, Mom, you don't have to explain anything. I get it.
你需要空间  其实迪恩也需要
You need space. And -- and so does Dean, you know?
他就是...
I-I mean, he -- he's just...
你刚回到我们身边
We just got you back,
他就是担心我们会再失去你
and he's just scared we're gonna lose you again,
你会因为我们是猎人而抛下我们
that -- that because we're Hunters, you're gonna walk away.
但我知道不会是那样的
But I know that's not true.
光是看看这些
Even looking at these...
你1980年救了阿沙
I mean, you saved Asa in 1980,
那是迪恩出生后
after Dean was born,
是大家都以为你已经退出猎魔之后
after everyone thought you quit hunting.
看来你当时无法停手
Seems like you couldn't stop then, and...
我猜你现在也停不下来
I'm guessing you can't stop now either.
这份工作  这种生活
This job, this life...
很疯狂
it's crazy and insane.
但也是我们的天性
But it's in our blood.
走吧
Come on.
我们去哪
Where we going?
跟阿沙道别
To say goodbye to Asa.
阿沙很喜欢那辆吉普
And Asa loved that Jeep.
保险丝熔断  燃油管线坏掉
Fuses were shorted, fuel line was busted.
他才不在乎
Ah, he didn't care.
他卷起袖子就修
He'd just roll up his sleeves, he'd get right to work.
各位  我们得马上走了
Guys, we need to leave now.
-萨姆  -兰迪死了
- Sam? - Randy's dead.
怎么回事
What happened?
有人杀了他  还把他绑在了天花板上
Someone gutted him and roped him to the ceiling.
就是这样
That's what happened.
有人知道水怎么停了吗
Anyone know why the water's shut off?
那是什么味儿
God, what's that smell?
硫磺
Sulphur.
等等
Wait.
-是恶魔  -对
- It's a demon. - ‭Yeah.
-是他  -他
- It's him. - ‭Him?
雅亿  一个十字路口恶魔
Jael. He's a crossroads demon.
他喜欢吊死人  他的癖好
And he hangs people. It's his thing.
扭断脖子  割喉
Snaps their neck, slits their throat.
他很不是东西
He's a real piece of work.
-吊死  阿沙那样吗  -是他杀了他
- Hanging? Like with Asa? - He's the one that killed him.
-该死  -我来
- Son of a bitch. - ‭Let me.
你们在浪费时间
You're wasting your time.
整栋房子都有符文  里外都有
The whole house has been warded, inside and out.
-什么意思  -我们困住了
- What does that mean? - It means we're trapped.
走开
Go away.
你不能指挥我
You're not the boss of me.
比莉
Billie.
-你来干什么  -收魂
- What're you doing here? - ‭My job.
我还没死呢
I'm not dead yet.
真可惜
Shame.
但实际上  我刚在里面收了一个
But actually, I just finished inside.
我收了个新鲜的灵魂
I was reaping a fresh soul.
97年那会儿
Look, back in '97,
阿沙去黄刀办件案子
Asa was working this case in Yellow Knife, all right.
原住民女孩被附身
A possession of a First Nations girl.
后来情况很糟  很血腥
Got real bad, real bloody.
是雅亿吗
Was it, uh, Jael?
阿沙驱逐了他  但雅亿还是杀了那女孩
Asa exorcised him, but not before Jael killed the girl.
她逼她给自己套上绞索
He made her tie a noose around her neck
还逼阿沙看着
and he made Asa watch.
萨姆  萨姆
Sam. Sammy!
随你怎么吹气
You can huff and puff,
那房子被超自然力量封锁了
but that house is on supernatural lockdown.
他们都听不到你喊
They can't even hear you.
好吧  驱魔不像用天使之刃
All right, an exorcism, it ain't like an Angel Blade.
-不是永久性的  -是啊
- Yeah, it's not permanent. - Exactly.
五年后  雅亿
Right, so five years later, Jael --
他回来向阿沙复仇了
he came back and he came for Asa.
怎么回事
How so?
阿沙当时在约会个女人  她有个孩子
Asa was seeing this woman, right? She had a kid --
-马琳  -对  马琳
- Marlene. - ‭Yeah, Marlene.
雅亿附身了她
Jael got into her.
他不管他是不是杀人了
It didn't matter that he was killing people,
他就是要阿沙知道这是私人恩怨
he wanted Asa to know it was personal.
他以此为乐
He gets off on it.
现在他来到了这儿
Yeah, and now he's here,
附身了一个人
possessing someone.
但是谁呢
Yeah, but who?
兰迪死时艾莉西娅不在屋里
Alicia wasn't in the room when Randy died.
其余人都在
The rest of us were.
我是去拿酒了
I was getting a drink.
迪恩也不在
Dean wasn't in the room either.
要么是艾莉西娅要么是迪恩
So it's Alicia or Dean.
我没有
I'm not!
拿圣水泼我啊  看看会怎么样
Throw some holy water on me, see what happens.
有人带了吗
Anybody packin'?
我们可以做点
We can just make more.
不行  水停了
No, we can't. The water's off.
-她知道的  你知道这不行  -得了
- She knew it. You knew that. - Oh, come on.
你做了什么
What did you do?
不是我  我可不亲自动手  这是规矩
It wasn't me. I don't get my hands dirty. Rules.
我只负责善后
I just clean up the mess.
不过  跟你说  看到温家人
Still, between us, it's always nice to see
不能如愿总是很爽的
a Winchester who can't get what he wants.
你觉得这好玩吗
You think this is funny?
里面的猎人要死了
Hunters are dying in there.
谁都有一死
Everyone dies.
我觉得迪恩还在屋外
I think Dean's still outside.
那就...缩小范围了
‭That does narrow it......down.
艾莉西娅
Alicia?
艾莉西娅现在不在
Alicia's not here right now.
留言吧
Leave a message. ‭
你们真有意思
Oh, you're a fun group.
我们今晚会玩得很高兴的
We're gonna have a good time tonight.
-它走了  -艾莉西娅
- It's gone. - Alicia, are you...
它没走  只是不在艾莉西娅体内了
It's not gone. It's just not in Alicia anymore.
洛琳  房子里还有别人吗
Loraine, is there anyone else in the house?
我不知道  今天一天都人来人往的
I don't know. People have been coming and going all day.
好吧  我们组对儿  搜索全屋
Okay, we're gonna pair off, we're gonna search the house --
找人  不是恶魔
for people, not for demons.
如果你找到了恶魔  大喊  我们来找你
You find a demon, yell. We'll find you.
如果你的搭档被附身  就跑
And if your partner gets possessed, run.
-妈妈  -走吧
- Mom. - Come on.
待在这儿
Stay here.
你进去过
You got in there.
你进去收那个灵魂来着  你可以带我进去
You got in to reap that soul. You can get me in.
我大概是可以
I could, I suppose.
-但是  -带我进去
- But - ‭Do it!
但是  是单程票
But it's a one-way ticket.
你要欠我个人情
And you're gonna owe me one.
我给你拿了杯双份的
I got you a double.
老天爷
Holy...
我弟弟呢
Where's my brother?
等等  你怎么...
Hey, hold up. How did you --
他就是恶魔
He's the demon!
-恶魔  -杀了他
- Demon? - ‭Kill him!
放松  女士
Easy, lady.
我不是恶魔  我是好人
Look, I'm not a demon, okay. I'm one of the good guys.
跟我走  听我的
Now stick with me, do what I say,
大家都能活着出去  都能
and everybody'll get out of here, okay? Everybody.
好吧
Well...
不是都能
not everybody.
你个恶魔还挺迟钝的
You're kind of slow for a demon, aren't you?
小心了
Careful now.
你会伤我感情的
You'll hurt my feelings,
我可能会发火
and I might lash out.
你下地狱去吧
How about you go to Hell?
得了  下面根本是一团乱
Please. It's a complete train wreck down there.
没有路西法  没有克劳力  乱糟糟的
No Lucifer, no Crowley. It's messy.
不  我是说  真的  下地狱
No, I mean, really, go to Hell.
[咒语]
驱魔
An exorcism?
埃维斯要走了
Elvis is leaving the building.
来来来
Come on. Come on. Come on.
萨姆
Sammy!
迪恩  我们以为你在外面
Dean, we thought you were outside.
-我又进来了  -怎么进来的
- Yeah, I got back in. - ‭How?
一次性的  不能重复了
It was a one-time deal. Won't happen again.
-都在了吗  -除了埃维斯
- Is this everybody? - Except for Elvis.
恶魔杀了他
Yeah, demon got him.
至少我们都有准备
Well, at least we're all prepared.
是啊
Yep.
厉害
Impressive.
-恶魔刃  能杀透  -好啊
- Demon Blade -- kills 'em dead. - Nice.
-我们得点蜡烛  -嗯  还有恶魔陷阱
- We gotta light some candles. - Yeah. A Devil's Trap.
-我去  -嗯
- On it. - Yep.
好  但我们怎么诱它进去
All right, uh, but how are we gonna lure it inside?
不用  我们进去
We're not. We get in.
大家都进去  大家都没问题
Everybody's in, everybody's clean.
如果有人不肯进去
If someone won't get in...
-那人就是恶魔  -正确
- They're the demon. - ‭That's right.
-机智  -谢谢
- Smart. - ‭Thanks.
什么样的恶魔陷阱
What kind of a Devil's Trap?
标准五角星  不弄什么花哨的
Standard pentagram. Nothing fancy.
我喜欢火星五芒星
I like a Fifth Pentacle of Mars.
更有个性
It's got more character.
因为个性现在很关键
Because character is what really matters right now.
萨姆
Sam...
这是挺尴尬  我知道
This is awkward, I'm owning that. But
但我觉得恶魔在你妈妈体内
the demon... I think it's in your mom.
她看上去没什么问题啊
She looks okay to me.
我虽然知道的不多
I may not know much,
但我知道看是看不出谁被附身了
but I know people don't "Look" possessed.
不  你们开始说恶魔陷阱时
No, I saw her sneak out of the room
我看到她偷溜了出去
when you started talking about the Devil's Trap.
她去了哪
Where did she go?
我知道她是你家人  但是  萨姆
I mean, I know she's family, but, Sam...
怎么回事
What's going on?
乔迪觉得是妈妈
Jody thinks that Mom --
不是觉得  是确定
No, I don't think. I know.
我知道她是恶魔
I know she's a demon!
杀了她  用刀  快杀了她
Kill her! Use the knife! Kill her now!
等等
Wait.
等等  乔迪  你...
Hold on a second. Jody, you...
你口气不像你自己
You don't sound like yourself.
因为那不是她
That's because she's not herself.
是吧
Are you?
总得试试
Can't blame a girl for tryin'.
我本来特希望你们杀了自己的妈妈
I had so hoped you'd kill your mom!
那多棒啊
Wouldn't that be a riot?
是啊  超级好玩
Yeah, super fun.
别想
No.
还有谁
Anybody else?
没了吗
Nope?
好吧
Fine.
-不  妈妈  -你干什么
- No! Mom! ‭- What are you doing?!
她是恶魔  我们杀恶魔
She's a demon. We kill demons.
-不  她是乔迪  -无聊了
- No, but she's Jody. - Boring!
我听过那么多你们温家人的传言
Oh, I have heard so many stories about you Winchesters.
而且
And...
我超级希望路西法的事是真的
I desperately want the Lucifer thing to be true.
他居然留了一具肉身一条活路
The idea that he left a meat suit alive
多么软弱啊
is just so deliciously weak.
至于你们其他人  我进过你们的大脑
As for the rest of you, I have been inside your heads.
我非常了解你们
I know all about you!
比如  双胞胎  不敢告诉别人
For example, the twins -- too frightened to tell anyone
他们其实是来跟爸爸道别的
that they actually came to say goodbye to their daddy.
还有悲伤的母亲
Or the grieving mother
那么讨厌儿子做猎人
who hated the fact that her son was a Hunter so much,
以至于把他的工具藏起来  破坏的他吉普
she'd hide his gear, she'd sabotage his Jeep,
就为了制止他猎魔
anything to keep him from hunting.
虽然根本没用
Not that it worked.
怎么不更努力些
Could've tried harder, huh?
还有这具你们这么在意的肉身
And this...meat suit you all seem to care so much about,
她还幻想跟阿沙过一辈子
she actually fantasized about a life with Asa.
能相信吗
Can you believe that?
那个废物男人
Like that worthless man --
闭上你的臭嘴
Shut your filthy mouth --
还有你
And you...
巴奇
Bucky.
勇敢的巴奇
Brave, brave Bucky.
我那晚也在
I was there that night.
跟这些善良的蠢蛋说说你做了什么
Tell these nice, stupid people what you did.
告诉他们你夺走了我的什么
Tell them what you took from me.
阿沙本是我的
Asa was mine.
[咒语]
别想
No.
[咒语]
告诉他们
Tell them! ‭
[咒语]
我杀了他  是我杀了阿沙
I killed him! I killed him. I killed Asa.
[咒语]
乔迪  你没事吧
Jody, you okay?
太难受了
That...sucked.
巴奇  你做了什么
Bucky, what did you do?
阿沙  他总是...
Asa, he was just al--
他总是那么固执
He was just always so stubborn.
听着  我们当时在林子里
Look... we were in the woods.
雅亿  他在逗弄他
Jael, he -- he was taunting him.
阿沙想去追他  但他没拿天使之刃
Asa wanted to chase him, but he didn't have the Angel Blade.
我说  "我们回去吧"
I said, "Let's go back."
他说我是懦夫  还推开了我
He called me a coward and he shoved me,
我就推了回去  他摔倒了
so I shoved him back, and he fell...
-撞到了头  -阿沙
- ...and he hit his head. - ‭Asa?
我不是有意的
I didn't mean to do it.
-就是误伤  -阿沙
- But it was a mistake. - ‭Asa. Asa!
是个意外
An accident.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不知道该如何是好
I didn't know what to do.
阿沙那么恨那个恶魔
Asa hated that damn demon so much that I just...
所以你觉得大家会相信是雅亿杀了他
Oh, you thought that people would buy that Jael killed him?
所以你把你的死党吊了起来  好掩盖自己的过失
So you hung your best friend to cover your own ass.
你们要把我怎么样
What are you gonna do to me?
告诉每个人  每个我们认识的猎人
Tell everyone, every Hunter we meet.
他们会知道你的  巴奇  知道你做了什么
They're gonna know your name, Bucky, know what you did.
你喜欢传说
You like stories?
今后  这就是关于你的传闻了
This is the story everyone's gonna tell about you. Forever.
我错了
I was wrong.
阿沙的确有家庭
Asa did have a family.
甚至有孩子
He even had kids.
我有孙辈了
I've got grandchildren.
或许我该去认识一下他们
Suppose I should go meet them.
抱歉
Sorry.
我经历过更糟的
I've had worse.
我不知道你和你儿子之间是怎么回事
I don't know what's going on between you and your boys,
但作为母亲  我要说
but I gotta tell you, mom to mom...
他们是好人
they are good men.
我见过的最好的
Best I've ever met.
我知道
I know.
问题不在他们
They're not the problem.
妈妈
Mom?
你没事吧
You okay?
她有事
She's really not.
比莉
Billie.
谁
Who's...
她是个死神
She's a Reaper.
是她把我送回了屋里
She's the one that got me back inside.
现在你欠我个人情了
And now you owe me one.
就她
This one.
就是她
This one right here.
什么
What?
我坚信死了的不该活过来
See, I'm a big believer in what dies, stays dead.
宇宙法则什么的
Laws of the universe and all that, so...
又不是我想回来的
I didn't ask to come back here.
是啊
No, you didn't.
而且你很不爽
And you hate it.
你那眼神  我见过
The look in your eyes, I've seen it before.
是死人的眼神
It's a dead man's look --
在说着  不管你去哪  不管你做什么
eyes that say no matter where you go or what you do,
感觉都好像这世界容不下你
it feels like this world doesn't fit anymore,
感觉好像你是一个人
like you're all alone.
她不是一个人
Well, she's not alone.
我说错了吗
Tell me I'm wrong.
我不是来伤害你的
I'm not here to hurt you.
我要给你个仁慈
I'm here to offer you mercy.
去楼上的单程票  远离这一切
A one-way ticket upstairs, away from all of this.
那要怎么做
How would it work?
妈妈
Mom.
你再杀我一遍吗
You just kill me again?
死神不杀人
Reapers don't kill people.
这是规矩
Rules.
这样啊
Well...
那么
then...
你只能等着了
Then I guess you're just gonna have to wait.
温家人啊
Winchesters.
如果你改主意了
If you change your mind --
如果你们任何一个改主意了
if any of you change your minds --
你们知道我叫什么
you know my name.
那么你要回家了吗
Does this mean you're coming home?
嗯
Yeah.
现在还不行  我还再需要点时间
Not quite yet. I just need a little more time.
我们能至少请你吃早餐吗
Can we buy you breakfast, at least?
-培根  -管饱
- Bacon? - ‭All the bacon.
好啊
I would love that.